234next.com 2010-12-12

# Privacy

**

### Privacy Policy for Timbuktu Media (and its affiliate websites, including 234NEXT.com)

**

**Summary**

Thank you for visiting 234NEXT.com, a Timbuktu Media Limited website. We truly value your privacy and have prepared this overview to explain what our online practices are, and to also explain how the information that we collect is used by 234NEXT.com, or its parent website, TimbuktuMedia.com.

It is important for us at Timbuktu Media that we continuously improve our understanding of our consumers. The personal information that we collect on our website is critical to ensuring that we provide the consumer with the best products and services at all times. It also enables us to provide data to potential and existing advertisers who are attempting to reach target audiences. This overview of our Privacy Policy covers the collection and use of information about our consumers online, through our websites, and offline, through our print publications.

**Collection of Information**

At 234NEXT.com, you are able to express your thoughts about something you read on the website or a blog or online forum, place orders for products and services, participate in polls, subscribe to the print publication of NEXT, as well as email newsletters from NEXT, and participate in periodic promotional offers. Timbuktu Media only obtains personal information to enable a better understanding of our consumers, especially the Nigerian demographic. The personal information that we may request from our consumers include:

  * Name of the consumer
  * E-mail Address
  * City
  * Country
  * Post/Zip Code

In some specific situations (for example, in the case of a promotional offer that is associated with a print subscription), we may also request a mailing address and telephone number. There may also be instances where we conduct surveys to evaluate the interest of the consumer in some products and services, or gauge their familiarity with various products.

**Opting In / Out**

Timbuktu Media always provides you with an opportunity to opt in (submit to personal information requests) or opt out (request to be removed from a subscription list). This is at the request of the consumer. It is also important to note that the personal information is now shared with anyone, and it is not provided to third party vendors.

**Use of Information**

Information that we collect on the website may be used in a variety of ways: 

  * \- To respond to requests for our products and services
  * \- To answer questions about our product offerings
  * \- To create an awareness of other products and services that we are offering
  * \- To better understand who our consumers are, and use this information to educate our advertising partners of who our consumers are and what their interests are.
  * \- To analyze web traffic
  * \- To personalize our offerings for our consumers

Personal information is available only to Timbuktu Media employees and independent contractors that are in the employ of Timbuktu Media and have a business need to view or access this information. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our promotional offers or when we make changes to our subscriber information, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. The information we collect in connection with your participation in our online forums, blogs and other online communities is used to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

In the event that you choose to submit content for publication (for example, a letter to our editors, comments or postings to an online forum, etc., we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

In some cases, we may conduct informal surveys to gather information that does not identify the individual, but which allows us to collect data and comments that improves the user interface and navigation of the entire website. This information also enables us to make better decisions about the content we have on our websites and the way that it is presented.

**Personal Information Storage and Security**

Personal information that is collected remains with Timbuktu Media. It may only be transferred if Timbuktu Media, NEXT or any of its affiliates is acquired by another company or sold or merged with another organization. Employees and independent contractors that are in the employ of Timbuktu Media and its affiliates are required to protect personal information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy. Processes are in place to ensure that personal information is not disclosed inappropriately, although we are not able to completely assure that information will not be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with our policy. 

It is possible that other companies may want to market their products and services to our consumers and may ask that we disclose personal information that we have collected. Our goal will be to give our consumers the option to opt in for these products and services and we will not sell your information to these companies. To ensure that we build comprehensive profiles of our consumers, we may sometimes analyze information that is collected online with external records so that we improve our marketing efforts. If you have registered on our websites, and choose not to receive marketing information, you will have the option to "unsubscribe" which follows marketing e-mails and other e-mail newsletters.

Timbuktu Media leverages all technical, personnel and physical security measures to protect personal information from being lost, stolen or inappropriately disclosed or altered.

**Links to Other Sites**

Timbuktu Media, 234NEXT.com and other accompanying websites has links to other websites either through strategic partnerships or affiliate relationships. Timbuktu Media and all of the websites it owns cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. Consumers are encouraged to have an increased awareness of the privacy policies of these other websites about how they collect personal information as they leave our website(s). This privacy policy applies solely to Timbuktu Media and all of its websites, and to the information that we collect there.

**Correction or Deletion of Information**

You are able to contact Timbuktu Media or 234NEXT.com by sending email to [ support@timbuktumedia.com.](mailto:support@timbuktumedia.com.)

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

Timbuktu Media periodically updates its privacy policy for its corporate and affiliate websites. You can always find information on our websites about any material changes we have to the policy. Consumers are asked to visit the privacy policy page at any time so view how we collect personal information and how we use this information.

This Privacy Policy was finalized on December 7, 2008 and posted on December 15, 2008. Updates will be made as needed but the policy is scheduled to be reviewed on a quarterly basis.
